hrdepartment.com 2013-02-11

# Your Privacy Rights

Monster collects personal information about you and distributes that information to help you connect with employers and other job seekers with similar interests and to provide other services to you. This policy describes how information is collected and distributed and your choices with respect to your personal information. Please review our full Privacy Statement for detailed information on our information and privacy practices.

## How Information is Used

Information you post in public areas of the site or placed in the searchable Resume database will be accessed, used, and stored by others around the world. We strive to provide a safe, secure environment by attempting to limit access to our database to legitimate users, but cannot guarantee that unauthorized parties will not gain access. We also cannot control how authorized users store or transfer information downloaded from the database, so you should ensure that you do not post sensitive information to Monster.

We use the information we collect about you to deliver the products and services we offer, and to operate and improve our sites. Our services include the display of personalized content and advertising on our site or other sites with which we have a business relationship. We may use your information to contact you about Monster site updates, conduct surveys, or informational and service-related communications, including important security updates.

## Disclosure of Information to Others

We share your information with third parties who help us in the delivery of our own products and services to you. These third parties may not use that information for any purpose other than assisting us in providing those products and services. 

If you have consented for us to do so, we may use your information to contact you about other products or services available from our affiliates. 

If you have consented for us to do so, we may also share your information with third parties who may contact you about their products or services. 

We also share information where legally required. Information collected on our Sites is stored in whole or in part in the United States, and may be subject to U.S. law. 

We may disclose and transfer information if our business is sold or acquired.

## Your Choices About Your Information

You may review, correct, or delete the personal information you submit to us at any time. Simply log into your account, go to your account profile, and make the necessary changes. We will delete your personal information, but will retain logs, demographic and statistical information about you and keep an anonymous, archived copy of your information. If your personal information was previously accessed by others using our web sites, we are unable to delete the information from their systems. 

Monster has no control over the information that Ad Networks or other third parties may have about you. We encourage you to visit their web sites and review and read the privacy policies and opt-out practices that govern their usage. 

If you change your mind about receiving communications from Monster or other parties, you may change your preferences by logging into your account. 

You may also turn off cookies in your browser. This may affect your use of the web site. 

## Important Information

Please review the full Privacy Statement for further information. 

Our Sites are not intended for children under 13 years of age. 

We participate in the U.S. Department of Commerce’s Safe Harbor Framework and we are a member of TRUSTe.

For more information on how to protect yourself online, visit our [Security Center](http://my.monster.com/securitycenter/ "Security Center More Detail Link").

## How to Contact Us

You may [contact us](http://about.monster.com/privacy/emailform/ "Contact Us More Detail Link") for questions or concerns about our privacy practices or the Safe Harbor program. You may also call us at 1-800-MONSTER, or write to us at: 

Privacy Office  
Monster Worldwide, Inc.  
5 Clock Tower Place, 5th Floor  
Maynard, MA 01754

If your question is not properly addressed, you may contact TRUSTe for assistance in resolving your issue.
